<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SettingsBlock>
	<ModSettings Class="ShitRimWorldSays.Settings">
		<database>
			<quotes>
				<li>
					<author>epserdar</author>
					<body>or is their explosion limited to deliberate injury?

edit: jesus christ i'm sorry

edit 2: guys stop awarding this like seriously, go donate to ur favorite mod author's patreon or smth</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ki22gs/noob_question_dont_upvote_do_homophobes_explode/</permalink>
					<score>184</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>el_chapo74</author>
					<body />
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/kgogh5/how_many_organs_can_i_remove_before_my_prisoner/</permalink>
					<score>186</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>MatunReddit</author>
					<body>I would like to entertain my colony by building a gladiator arena and forcing prisoners to duel, then making the winner eat his own body parts and organs in form of human meat surimi, and then beat the nugget to death with a shotgun stock. (i already have a mod for that.) So im looking for a duel mod. Thanks! 
Edit: Thanks for the arena mod, i already forced a man who won a fight to the death to eat his opponent and then himself.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/kdiwm1/is_there_a_mod_that_allows_forcing_prisoners_to/</permalink>
					<score>291</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Konebred</author>
					<body>"Pemmican is full of nuts"

"I would love to taste your nuts"</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/kb2bnf/you_can_tell_they_really_wanted_an_excuse_to_fuck/gfe4le0/</permalink>
					<score>166</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ProtossHueretes</author>
					<body>Is there a relationship penalty if I sell the organs of prisoners back to their home colony? : RimWorld</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/kamln3/is_there_a_relationship_penalty_if_i_sell_the/</permalink>
					<score>236</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>arquillion</author>
					<body>I always keep a prisonner without spine around, they dont cause any problem and if im missing any parts, they are right here with their spaghetti noodle back</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/k917ng/someone_is_about_to_lose_both_of_their_legs_in_a/gf2m6iq/</permalink>
					<score>353</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Hobbvots</author>
					<body>**Type 1 player:** "My brutal Randy -40c ice sheet cannibal had his penis ripped off as an eldrich horror manhunter pack. I just had my slave labour human leather hat factory up and running too."    


**Type 2 player:** "I built Dublin Castle, but I added some comfy rooms for my guys."</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/k7o8ue/two_very_different_types_of_colony_experiences/gesdl2o/</permalink>
					<score>354</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Trafalgar_Law29</author>
					<body>I tried to save him and make him leave the tile safely. I helped him up a few times when he got malnourished but had to deal with an infestation and forgot about him. He died doing what he loved, wandering around confused due to dementia.

https://preview.redd.it/ekcd0t86ww261.jpg?width=1920&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=82453b284385f5766ea63693065e6dc3f05d3d19</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/k5rkyd/this_is_the_slowest_person_i_have_ever_seen_he/</permalink>
					<score>256</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Hates_Worn_Weapons</author>
					<body>Perhaps you shouldn't let your husky perform surgery. Everybody knows Alpacas are the true surgeons of the animal kingdom.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/k1yxw8/how_are_you_still_alive/gdreg3j/</permalink>
					<score>247</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>alebaf</author>
					<body>I let my animals graze around all the map to avoid malnutrition. My labradors are starving anyway. After a while I confined them in the hay stockpile but they didn't eat it. The only things they seems to eat are animals' bodies.

Is there a solution to this? It would be a shame to slaughter them, they are much better than turtles as guard animals!</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jyvj2h/labradors_wont_eat_grass_neither_the_hay_i_grew/</permalink>
					<score>154</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Lejobo</author>
					<body />
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jqll4h/is_it_possible_to_harvest_the_liver_or_spine/</permalink>
					<score>278</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Lii-Love</author>
					<body>Social fights are just surprise melee training</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hjnwjd/bloodlust_is_perhaps_the_best_trait_in_the_game/fwnn8ie/</permalink>
					<score>209</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Goodpie2</author>
					<body>Rectal Arrow Procedures</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/jvpbo2/rectal_arrow_procedures/</permalink>
					<score>490</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Prototype2001</author>
					<body>I'm gonna need more cannibals.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/9p7i88/im_gonna_need_more_cannibals/</permalink>
					<score>287</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>redxlaser15</author>
					<body>The flesh of an infant is the best, much more tender and delicious.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jq75s3/yeah_the_baby_does_look_like_you_sweetie/gbljr2l/</permalink>
					<score>163</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Lord_Of_Coffee</author>
					<body>Or, or, hear me out: a good basement goblin.

Resources are delivered to him, he churns out sculptures. Little to no interaction with others, only to deliver new resources and give up art.

Have some pawns with non-lethal weapons to rough-house him a bit and bring him back in line when he gets some seditious thoughts of burning shit or snorting Yayo.

Then send a doctor in to treat the broken bones and shattered pelvis and go from there.

Edit: Someone replied about feeding the Goblin kibble and having it sleep in a terrible cell with no bed or furnishings to make him suffer. I had a reply typed up, but the comment I was replying to was deleted. I'm not tossing my reply, sooooooo: 

Inefficient. Wasteful. Affects art quality, availability. No. The Goblin will learn that by behaving well and doing good work, its cage will be gilded. Exceptional work may yield a night's embrace of mother cocaine. Bad work and misbehavior means her embrace leaves him, his gilded furnishings become scrap tin. What is given can be taken away, after all. It will be conditioned by this. Live by it, fear repercussions. Work itself past exhaustion for that reward it seeks. The embrace, her caress, a momentary escape.

To coincide with her embrace is the allure of the flames of the father. His glorious light and the crackling sounds he makes will lull the Goblin to sleep. Knowing the fire is there, it is with it. All is beautiful polished stone, but this lone torch and the wood used to fuel it. Nothing burns but the vessel of the father.

To misbehave is to lose this fire. To be deprived of the flames of the father. This torch, his vessel, the one solace it has for the darker thoughts of its mind. The primal carnal adoration and adulation of its warm glow. The goblin will know this, and so with worn down bleeding hands, it will work. Sculpt, create what comes to its warped mind as it loses sanity addled by the embrace that slowly kills it. The fire that soon develops new colors, speaks to it, whispers to it, voices in the cold dark stone cell.

[\(Credit to the original basement Goblin greentext for the source inspiration\)](https://knowyourmeme.com/photos/1002565-the-sims)</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jq47ju/never_have_i_seen_such_a_worthy_candidate_to/gbjp92t/</permalink>
					<score>207</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>toadofsteel</author>
					<body>Didn't watch Parks &amp;amp; Rec all that much and didn't get the reference before someone below linked the video.

Now that I've seen it...

&amp;gt; This is outrageous. Where are the armed men who come in to take the raiders away? Where are they? This kind of behavior is never tolerated in MountainFuckHole. You have a Firestarting Spree like that they turn you to chemfuel. Right away. No trial, no nothing. Pacifists, we have a special chemfuel for pacifists. You are pigging out: right to chemfuel. You are insulting someone leading to social fighting: right to chemfuel, right away. Walking too fast: chemfuel. Slow: chemfuel. You are charging too high prices for dusters, cowboy hats: you right to chemfuel. You undercook muffalo? Believe it or not, chemfuel. You overcook insect jelly, also chemfuel. Undercook, overcook. You make an appointment to install a bionic arm and you don't show up, believe it or not, chemfuel, right away. We have the best colonists in the world because of chemfuel.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jjmvno/epoe_in_a_nutshell/gafazr0/</permalink>
					<score>244</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>GetAJobCheapskate</author>
					<body>There is a mod that enables harvesting bone from prisoners, to build furniture. If you would have a chair made from his legs, engraved with his capture, that would be close to rimworlds purest essence.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jnyvnd/a_prisoner_of_mine_is_in_his_prison_cell_with_a/gb4sb9l/</permalink>
					<score>191</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Perolith</author>
					<body>On the other hand, ketchup is an *excellent* source of chemfuel. So by growing tomatoes, you can literally send your son's ship to space via ketchup.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jkfpvh/prisoner_recruitment/galogd9/</permalink>
					<score>214</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>toadofsteel</author>
					<body>Why not both? Construct the bionics for your own colonists, then harvest the prisoners organs and sell them. Then butcher them, convert the meat to chemfuel, and sell the chemfuel and leather.

The best war crimes are the ones where you make a fuckton of money.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jjmvno/epoe_in_a_nutshell/gae2rzo/</permalink>
					<score>257</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Pax_Humana</author>
					<body>"Legs are a privilege, not a right."</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jirk8k/this_is_what_happens_when_your_psychic/ga93854/</permalink>
					<score>300</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>youcantdothatheresir</author>
					<body>I shoot as soon as they go into withdrawal. 

Or I make "rehab" facilities, which is a triple thick granite box with no doors full of packaged survival meals. They emerge free from withdrawal and addiction(sometimes catatonic)</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jiflzx/no_youre_fucking_not/ga7gkxi/</permalink>
					<score>334</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>FadeCrimson</author>
					<body>That's what I meant when I said 'popsicle'. You give them one single peg-leg to flop their way through the dirt with blindly.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/j7pbwz/how_to_scare_an_enemy_faction_a_simple_tutorial/g86skhk/</permalink>
					<score>220</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>JC12231</author>
					<body>Fuck I said that wrong.

Reverse the order of my sentence lol, I meant killing the single animal was much worse than the torture and murder of thousands.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jeiyob/so_you_have_chosen_death/g9gorxq/</permalink>
					<score>171</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>zekromNLR</author>
					<body>Yes actually - about 1650 (market value) from the harvestable organs, and another 210 from the leather - or over 1000 up to 3000 (depending on quality, assuming at least normal) if that is made into a duster.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/jc8n5l/do_you_guys_like_my_workshop/g90gm2n/</permalink>
					<score>162</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>possibly_not_a_bot</author>
					<body>I ended up solving this by installing Simple Slavery and keeping an immobile lobotimised slave around to make sure my robots can keep building. Thanks anyway!</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/j9c71t/unable_to_construct_anything_via_misc_robots_when/g8j49zq/</permalink>
					<score>334</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Taotipper</author>
					<body>I generally like refugees, but recently I had a reward off for killing all of them that I thought was too good to pass up.  I couldn't figure out how to make this work. If I manually kill any of them then the entire quest fails, including the betrayal request. There doesn't seem to be an obvious way to mark the refugees as hostile, or to accept the betrayal option. Am I missing something?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/j61az4/typical_tuesday_tutorial_thread_october_06_2020/g7vqolh/</permalink>
					<score>282</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ProtossHueretes</author>
					<body>How to force someone to falling in love? : RimWorld</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/iw5s0j/how_to_force_someone_to_falling_in_love_rimworld/</permalink>
					<score>189</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>LeHeartgasm</author>
					<body>It's only gay if the skin of their penises are sewn together in the duster!</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/iojuc8/lmao/g4es1do/</permalink>
					<score>325</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>contactlite</author>
					<body>Open the developer tools and bomb them a couple times then revive them and launch them at their enemies to watch them get their shit pushed in over and over again. It’s what any sane person would do.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/imxvlj/its_payback_time_cassandra_phoebe_and_randy_are/g44sl7d/</permalink>
					<score>268</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Trogladonis</author>
					<body>I had a colonist named Gnugfur once and he cheated on his wife. I proceeded to use one of my dubious medical mods to have her surgically transform Gnugfur into a biological woman; womb and all.

He wasn't very pleased about it when he woke up.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ik3tat/reunion_part_3_080/g3jdft3/</permalink>
					<score>415</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>IONASPHERE</author>
					<body>Top tip, give them peglegs and then remove them. They can't leave their hospital bed, and as long as they have TV/decent hospital/weed they'll be happy enough. 40% mood might still be tough, but it completely prevents mental breaks. Great for breaking a addiction from one of your own pawns, especially if you've biotic legs for when they recover</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ijaxy3/bruh_what/g3e6a4e/</permalink>
					<score>313</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Rim_Job_Joe</author>
					<body>Hi guys, I have install psychology mod firstly. I have a few colonists (about 6) and recently captured a fews of slave from a trader. They are all mostly happy and we were doing well. I keep them slaves in the back and they are nice as they keep the crops well and harvest my potatoes and weed. I am happy, and I treating them well as I giving them a lot of things to do like a horseshoe ring, a concrete floors and also I am put the ducks in there to keep them company.

My problems are that the slave keep running for mayor and my colonist keep electing them. I cannot stop democracy and I hate it. I just want to run my slaves and get the harvest without this happening. I get a notification from my game that the mayor processing is begin and that my two slaves are running for the office. I think to myself no this cannot happen so I lock them away so they cannot meeting the constituents but somehow one of them get elected anyway. So I am forced to building a desk in slave barracks and from now all my colonists runing into there to meet the mayor.

 Eventually the mayor getting so depressed he lock himself away into his room and try to kill his own self. Now with all this shit happen, I cannot to harvesting my crop and I am going to be in a big amount of shit again when the winter come. How doing I stop democracy from happen, or at least stop my slave from running for office?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ihsl2q/how_do_i_stop_my_slaves_from_running_for_mayor/</permalink>
					<score>373</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Rim_Job_Joe</author>
					<body>Thanks for your help, yes I am seeing now that the woman is menopausal and might be affecting the loving. I have the birds and bees mod yes. I had to getting rid of most of the women from my tribe as they were misandrist and hated men, unfortunate for me the ones who remain did not having a hate of men but were menopausal. But that's ok because she is a very good miner. I suppose I am now to maybe separate them into different beds as they are very depressed each time in the morning. 

I think they still have all the genitals, but he is having a scar on his penis. I could try to replacing with a new wooden penis if that would help.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/igibd1/do_proximity_to_grave_affect_sexual_pleasure_of/g2ufwt7/</permalink>
					<score>210</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Argument_Agitator</author>
					<body>Does proximity to a grave affect the sexual pleasure of colonists?</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/ihs536/does_proximity_to_a_grave_affect_the_sexual/</permalink>
					<score>292</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Gohrx</author>
					<body>That's why you send everyone but your local psycho on a nice walk around town (caravan). When they come back, there will be significantly fewer prisoners but more organs and a surprising amount of soft leather.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/if9h4a/what_the_hell_did_i_just_step_into/g2n42eg/</permalink>
					<score>437</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>auraswolf</author>
					<body>i like to remove the legs of any prisoners and put them anywhere i can (normally a small room) sex change any guys so my colonists can take out all there pent-up issues whenever they need and if any prisoners have kids ill check if they are worth keeping if not ill kill them at the feet of the mother and butcher them in the same room then force feed them said child. its also a great way of getting more bears and thrombos</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/icgl35/how_evil_are_you_whats_the_darkest_thing_youve/g230bed/</permalink>
					<score>211</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Rim_Job_Joe</author>
					<body>Hi guys, I need to move colony but I dont contains a lot of food. I sending half my colony away due to them hating men but they died when ambushed on the road. The men I have left cannot fall in love with each other and that actually brought me great sadness. I am getting attacked daily now by robot so have decided to move somewhere easier to defending as I am on snowy place with no mountain. As I dont have a lot of food, I cant feeding my warg who ate a lot of meat and cant eat the grass and the simple meals etc so if I bringing them with me they will all die of starvation or will eat all of the food I have. Then a thought come to me, can I transplant the brain of the mega sloth i tamed into warg to make it a vegan? That ways it can eating the berries on the come to the new place and wont eating the food from my men. If there is the mod for this I think it would help me? Thanks.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ic784c/can_i_make_my_wargs_vegan_by_transplanting_brains/</permalink>
					<score>259</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>lokvit</author>
					<body>WARNING: this image can cause sadistic joy</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ibd2p4/warning_this_image_can_cause_sadistic_joy/</permalink>
					<score>565</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ProtossHueretes</author>
					<body>Will ridding my colony of women turn my men into homosexual?</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/iammgr/will_ridding_my_colony_of_women_turn_my_men_into/</permalink>
					<score>319</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>AnUnladenSwallow_</author>
					<body>Do animals suffer mental break if you feed them their young?</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/i9qxen/do_animals_suffer_mental_break_if_you_feed_them/</permalink>
					<score>299</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>FnordMan</author>
					<body>&amp;gt; And kibble, don't waste man.

One of the things I love about this game. Most games there's an implied comma between waste and man.. this one? Heck nope!</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/i88yjm/i_love_rimworld_12_with_royalty_even_with_150/g17scew/</permalink>
					<score>211</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Royal_Sir_Masterton</author>
					<body>"If my pawns eat enough human, will they get used to it?"</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/i6m4qr/if_my_pawns_eat_enough_human_will_they_get_used/</permalink>
					<score>314</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>F33N1X</author>
					<body>Welcome to the Rim. Would you like human leather cowboy hats or nugget sex slaves?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ax78mv/nsfwheadsup_rimjobworld_nsfw_mod_is_too_much_of_a/ehs8qer/</permalink>
					<score>348</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ketra1504</author>
					<body>She has no legs and therefore no rights.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/i4wp9i/say_hello_to_kat_the_doctors_practice_dummy_what/g0l5fi0/</permalink>
					<score>251</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Rim_Job_Joe</author>
					<body>I build a z level with the mod because I want a zone to remove the penis etc. Basically I'll capture the slave, bring them underground, remove the penis and then release them just as I am about to break their willpower. But what I want to know is can I remove the penis or just neuter them with the game?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/i4z05b/how_to_build_a_penis_removal_room_in_the_z_levels/</permalink>
					<score>159</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>CaioPinho9</author>
					<body>I received a mission that I needed to keep a prisoner alive for one week in my colony, when I realized that I could do anything with him if he didn't die, I removed his legs so he wouldn't run away, took one arm, one eye, one lung, but I'm not a monster so before he left I put two wooden foot and a eye patch in him. In the end he was with -80 in mood because of organs harvested, at least he vented.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/i2wtdh/my_experiment_prisoner/</permalink>
					<score>283</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>EfficientSoup</author>
					<body>Send a colonist to beat up or open fire on the baby until it is unconscious and/or unable to move and you should be able to feed him afterwards since it will be unable to move and get out of his crib. Bonus melee/shooting and medical skill.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/i2e1zn/this_baby_is_throwing_himself_out_of_the_crib/g04oe2w/</permalink>
					<score>235</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Aldiirk</author>
					<body>Mindscrews can be removed with an operation. Failure can cause brain damage, though. ¯\\\_(ツ)\_/¯

I put a mindscrew and a psychic harmonizer in a prisoner in a cramped 2x2 cell set at 33C in an attempt to turn him into a sort of "beacon of agony" to project a powerful mood debuff on attacking raids. I removed his legs to prevent him from having mental breaks. However, the area of effect was only like 30 tiles, so it didn't work, and I ended up removing both brain implants (to get them back) before turning him into doctor practicve and harvesting his liver.

...maybe that's why half my colonists had chemical fascinations and did all the drugs. It was the only way to drown out the screams echoing from the cell....</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/i1z8uh/drugs_are_underrated/g01e4q3/</permalink>
					<score>455</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Theycallmetheherald</author>
					<body>Exactly, different beasts. 

Oni is about survival

Rimworld.. not so much.. it's about dying and killing and selling the lungs and left robotic eye of a raider you captured to buy more drugs for your ambrosia addicted dog.</body>
					<permalink>/r/Oxygennotincluded/comments/i12jvj/ever_played_rimworld/fzujjbe/</permalink>
					<score>294</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>TheRealFedral</author>
					<body>Gonna be absolute chaos. Groups with Doomsday launchers blowing up bases, harvesting organs, and disappearing into the night, leaving legless, armless, organless husks laying on the ground.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hz03nw/onlinecity/fzfwwh8/</permalink>
					<score>207</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>MonkeyTheBlackCat</author>
					<body>My new colony consists of one massively overpowered, near perfect glitter world guy.

No one else.

Apart from the one prisoner I test out all of the weird torturous weapons I find in the mod directory.

Is that bad?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hyvozq/am_i_a_bad_person/</permalink>
					<score>163</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Fredex8</author>
					<body>Given my penchant for performing unnecessary surgery on prisoners I'd be tempted to give a dozen prisoners peg legs and then upgrade the most beserk break prone prisoner to be fully bionic and keep them all in a small dark cell with only human meat for sustenance. I wonder how long the others would last before getting robot-ed to death.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/8upy2l/archotech_legs_are_awesome/e1haxl7/</permalink>
					<score>278</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ArkhielModding</author>
					<body>BTW, is there a mod allowing you to rip the face of a prisonner and wear it (with a mood when he sees it) ?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hxd104/when_a_person_says_they_dont_want_to_wear_a_face/fz67qt2/</permalink>
					<score>258</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>DaddySpongeBoi</author>
					<body>Don't worry, they also get their funding from prisoners who 'mysteriously' became organless popsicle people (1 peg leg).</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hx1qe1/hol_up/fz39dvy/</permalink>
					<score>239</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>NotABotCom</author>
					<body>Sometimes I wish RimWorld had kenshi like arm and leg dismemberment. I just wanna see a pawns limb get YEETED across the map from being shot by a uranium slug turret.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hvhzrp/a_rimworld_colonist/fyu7oot/</permalink>
					<score>317</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>dave2293</author>
					<body>Everything was going great. The external temperature was down to about 40c, the crops were coming in, and the barns were full. One last task before bed: have Hack butcher the extra corpses in the freezer. Even if the reserve freezer's power goes out (again), I want that leather.


Right before he finishes, I get a notification: Rhino Revenge. My tamer (skill 19) pissed off the rhino and got laid out. Her guard animals put up a good fight, and when she passed out, they went back to their barn to rest. My colonists start trying to recover poor Leyton.


Fast forward 5 mins. There are now 4 downed colonists and a nudist with a poor machine pistol standing over a dead rhino in the house. I start looking to see if she can actually stabilize anyone... and the explosions start.


Two of the injured guard animals were boomalopes. Since it was late evening when they bled out, all the other boomalopes were in the boomalope barn with them. The horses keep "rescuing" the injured, burning survivors by dragging them back into the barn.


Boom. Everything runs burning into the fields. Fires on animal goes out. Animal goes back into the barn. Boom.


In 10mins, I went from a stable colony in the badlands whose worst problem was the freezer being full to a nudist crafter standing in a bloodstained hall while the herds exploded all over the crops. 2020.


PS: I would like to report that the stone barn, built to keep the heat down so the boomalopes wouldn't get heatstroke, did survive the chained explosions. Strong recommend, lol.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hv5tdg/so_last_night_2020_hit_hard/</permalink>
					<score>269</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ripmorld</author>
					<body>I harvest their spine and give it back when they join.
It is much more space efficient</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hv45sm/unpopular_style/fyr0u1c/</permalink>
					<score>258</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ZehAngrySwede</author>
					<body>One death is a tragedy, one million deaths is a profit.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/huiqpv/could_i_interest_you_in_a_human_leather_chair/fypj27p/</permalink>
					<score>183</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>DrManton</author>
					<body>I wonder, if you butcher a bunch of merchants, make dusters out of their leather and gift them back to the faction - is the balance positive or negative?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/huiqpv/could_i_interest_you_in_a_human_leather_chair/fynayue/</permalink>
					<score>281</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Pyros51</author>
					<body>Goes to bed with his wife.

The next morning she wakes up to find a 300kg megaspider under the covers with her...</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/htwifn/meet_adele_my_newest_recruit_who_apparently_had_a/fyjtb86/</permalink>
					<score>223</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>SparlingFam1</author>
					<body>I pay for everything in corn and body parts.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/htorvx/creditdebt_or_yayo/fyi5fbm/</permalink>
					<score>185</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>arkman575</author>
					<body>... I’m fine with turning my disobedient colonists into living carpets and treating raider camps as necro-marts, but dude...you got issues.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ht8ymp/one_of_my_wargs_just_did_this_to_a_tortoise/fyfqvqb/</permalink>
					<score>279</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ripmorld</author>
					<body>It isn't human it's "synthetic" meat. - McDonald's manager</body>
					<permalink>/r/ShitRimworldSays/comments/hsvm1t/it_isnt_human_its_synthetic_meat_mcdonalds_manager/</permalink>
					<score>260</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>KoubuKai</author>
					<body>"Well, we've learned how to gruesomely profane the sanctity of the human mind by butchering someone like an animal, so that we may feed this abomination of silicon and sentience."

"Sure have. Now then, would you fancy a spot of cheese?"

"Why, I thought you'd never ask."</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hrbus6/my_colony_really_does_have_its_priorities_in_order/fy3gb55/</permalink>
					<score>276</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>MentalMallard28</author>
					<body>I can’t believe that some people let their prisoners have the mercy of death. I stick mine on life support, blow their brains out, and use them as a spigot for blood, which I use in place of medicine for autopsies. Harvesting organs while their alive is such a pain, it’s much easier when the flesh scan isn’t screaming and thrashing.</body>
					<permalink>/r/SpaceCannibalism/comments/hpqdur/and_that_sweet_sweet_meat/fxu5865/</permalink>
					<score>266</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>cotton961</author>
					<body>They don’t always help, I can’t remember exactly what happened since it was my first colony, but the man in black I got was nudist, brawler, and pyromaniac. 

I let the pawns kinda run themselves to see what would happen, after they were downed the man in black appears, saves them all, but... as they healed he would beat them back down until they were back in shock. After I forbade him from doctor, he simply killed the first 3 by beating them to death, and while the other two were in their bed unable to move.... he burned my whole house down with them inside. 

I got so mad I deleted the save and hopefully this monster with it, but I’m terrified he will one day reappear to exact revenge for being deleted. I’m so paranoid about it that if all my colonists are downed I just delete the save lol</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ho0wxl/it_all_started_when_kouhei_decide_to_eat_without/fxgj3ug/</permalink>
					<score>242</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Rookiebeotch</author>
					<body>I don't think you understand. The ocean wasn't named after Ivan's mistake.

Ivan made a mistake, and the consequence was the formation of a large ocean.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hniy6x/thatspretty_big/fxc7vcv/</permalink>
					<score>376</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Odd_Employer</author>
					<body>You put the right lung in, you take the right lung out, you put the right lung in and shake it all around!</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hmvf66/when_your_colonists_start_eating_kibble_instead/fx8y6k6/</permalink>
					<score>371</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>AmadeusV1</author>
					<body>Alright alright hear me out. So Randy's storyteller seems to want to keep things relatively balanced. I've noticed in my ~200 hours that sometimes Randy giveth, and sometimes Randy taketh, but the two usually come in pairs. Heat wave kills a colonist, Randy blesses me with supply drops shortly after. I had a great harvest, Randy gives me flash fires. 

So, to keep things in check, could it potentially be beneficial to sacrifice a colonist every once in a while?</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hm7yfz/in_theory_could_occasional_sacrifices_be/</permalink>
					<score>205</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>TheCockKnight</author>
					<body>I love a good drop pod raid.  CQC action, maximum casualties = maximum drama.  Headshots, blown off pinky fingers and all of my expensive shit exploding.  Makes my dick hard until they break my fucking flatscreen.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hl4abk/drop_pod_raid/fwx66nt/</permalink>
					<score>245</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>jws_shadotak</author>
					<body>Fun tip next time you need relations with a faction and you have one of their people:

You can get higher a higher relation bonus by removing all organs from the person and sending it all back to the faction. They like the body parts more than the person.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hk8xrp/2144_hours_to_realise_that_this_was_a_thing/fwrykkf/</permalink>
					<score>607</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>the_revised_pratchet</author>
					<body>Surprisingly its all in the lips. You really need to get a good seal going otherwise you won't be able to move onto the next stage. Once your lips are firmly around the eyesocket, increase suction until you feel the eyeball move outward and towards your teeth. When you feel enough of the eyeball has passed the tips of your teeth, clamp down firmly. Congratulations, you've bitten an eyeball out!</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hjnwjd/bloodlust_is_perhaps_the_best_trait_in_the_game/fwobas4/</permalink>
					<score>343</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Jelly_Noodle</author>
					<body>And no lights.

Edit: I deleted that colony because I was bored but I made a new colony which also has no tables and no lights.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hiim6c/i_have_no_tables_in_my_colony/</permalink>
					<score>165</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Dexter4111</author>
					<body>I dont see how helping hand needs all of his/hers organs? :&amp;gt;</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/kcx4nc/question_bout_recruiting_prisoners/gft3881/</permalink>
					<score>140</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Sorwest</author>
					<body>Humans sure be tasting like chicken</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/k70cic/sure_give_me_an_extra_30_colonists_to_manage/geo7te3/</permalink>
					<score>122</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>RuggyMasta</author>
					<body>They usually taste better, cause they’re marinated in the tears of the bonded colonist.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/j9d587/what_to_do_with_the_body_of_bonded_animals/g8j1k11/</permalink>
					<score>130</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>The_Flurr</author>
					<body>Same, my hospital will have medicine shelves, my workshops will have resource shelves, etc, that get replenished by hauler bears from deep storage.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/j7zacp/does_anybody_else_go_to_the_effort_of_making/g88o2a8/</permalink>
					<score>124</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>KoubuKai</author>
					<body>... can you make normal meals from the forbidden milk, or will that also make it a forbidden meal?

Because lavish meals filled to the brim with vitamins, minerals, and transformative nanites sounds like a great way to torment prisoners.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/j09xga/pawnmorpher_is_fun/g6qf3rm/</permalink>
					<score>102</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>CinderblockChewer</author>
					<body>They can keep then. I only really like baby hands.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/i2wtdh/my_experiment_prisoner/g0e0ubi/</permalink>
					<score>115</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Blytzkryeg</author>
					<body>Last play through I had, I managed to get 12 prisoners from a raid... When inevitably one of them had a break and started beating on things... I ended up popping in one of my pawns, fired an incendiary into the room and took care of all 12 potential problems... Wood floors, granite walls, and using the prison for chemfuel storage for the win.

\--Directly after the fire went out I got the royalty trader in, and I could have sold them all. Can't even use them for hats because you can't get skin from ashes. Maybe it wasn't a complete win.</body>
					<permalink>/r/SpaceCannibalism/comments/hsesbx/the_last_thing_my_prisoners_see_after_throwing_a/fyc4cpo/</permalink>
					<score>120</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>Chuntzy</author>
					<body>I always start good, but then that sweet taste of gold from organ harvesting takes over.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/hikm2q/colony_of_riveria_cass_hard_15_years_in/fwhtu2f/</permalink>
					<score>137</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>khearn</author>
					<body>Yup, every morning when the alarm goes off, I check the weather report to see if it will be a good day to hunt homophobes.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/ki22gs/noob_question_dont_upvote_do_homophobes_explode/ggq8dyh/</permalink>
					<score>114</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>CalmBalm</author>
					<body>One joint turned my colonist into an asthmatic duck</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/klisbh/dont_do_drugs_kids/gh9tyvz/</permalink>
					<score>172</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>ALE199ITA</author>
					<body>The Meat grinder from VFME calls for the blood of guinea pigs.</body>
					<permalink>/r/RimWorld/comments/kkm6m1/so_when_my_guinea_pigs_army_ate_all_the_grass_on/gh3vwmj/</permalink>
					<score>142</score>
				</li>
				<li>
					<author>beastebeat</author>
					<body>If you don't have prison labor I reccomend trying to get chicken morph and cow morph prisoners since their eggs and milk can be sold for quite a bit. Chickens will be easier early on since they lose a lot of manipulation with their wings.</body>
					<permalink>/r/SpaceCannibalism/comments/kj1zf2/warcrimes_are_best/gguwsu0/</permalink>
					<score>297</score>
				</li>
			</quotes>
		</database>
		<replaceGameTips>True</replaceGameTips>
		<minimumKarma>100</minimumKarma>
	</ModSettings>
</SettingsBlock>